I'm sorry. Okay. Keep going.
Well, then things got really bad.
The family that I was nannying for,
they had to move.
And that's what you do?
You're in child care?
Yeah. Well, that's what I love.
Um, I was going to school for it.
Uh, early education.
But then, you know, losing this job,
uh, it's just really hard financially.
Yeah, for sure.
But then I get this email
from my landlord saying,
"We're raising your rent. Good day."
I'm glad you came today.
You know, cases like yours are
exactly why my firm does these events.
So, this is what you do?
Pick fights with landlords?
My firm handles all kinds of housing
and real estate issues.
Keeping landlords honest, we do that...
We do that pro bono.
It's like a perk.
Um...
So, what are you doing here?
What do you mean?
You're about to pop.
Shouldn't you be home
drinking raspberry tea?
Well, that sounds very nice,
but, um, I'm managing.
People do it.
LA Law. There she goes.
Hi, Henry.
Please, Daddy.
I promise that Mama's home. I promise.
-Hi, Caitlin.
-Hey, Alison.
Um, where's the contract? I need it.
He says he's still proofreading.
I can call him again.
Uh...
I-I think we're gonna
have to pick this up later.
Oh. Is everything okay?
Uh, yeah. Um...
Yeah, I just think I'm going into labor.
Oh.
Just tell me. How are they not real?
-Where are my keys?
-Mom?
-Earth to Mom.
-Can you hold this a second?
Mom.
-What, the baby animals?
-Yeah.
-Because they're in a video game.
-It costs money.
Why would they cost money
if they're not real?
Yeah, that's exactly my question.
Let's make some space.
Mom, this is serious to me.
I know, honey. I know.
I know.
You're saying it's serious to you.
And I get it. But we need to go.
-Can you get in the car?
-I'm helping.
Okay. There we go.
-What are you doing?
You leave your baby
in the street?
You can't just
drive down here that fast.
Oh, you're lucky that stroller
didn't damage my car.
-Come on.
-Dumb bitch.
Oh, come on.
-Are we ready to do this?
-Dad.
-Jesus.
-What the hell?
-What happened?
-This woman...
She just came speeding down here.
-What a fucking idiot.
-Dad.
What? If it's true, you can say "fuck."
There should be a stop sign there.
-Yeah, well, LA.
-What does that mean?
-People don't stop in LA.
-Oh...
No, there should be a stop sign.
Thank you.
Okay. Tomatoes...
Okay, we're not buying those today.
Let's check out the apples over there.
Hmm.
Caitlin.
-Polly. Yeah.
-Polly. Right.
Wow. How are you?
I'm good. Yeah, I'm good.
What happened with your landlord?
Um, I sent him a letter,
but he said something about, you know,
the law with rent increase,
that unfortunately it doesn't apply.
Well, he's wrong.
-What you need to do is...
-It's fine.
You know, I'm-I'm getting by.
Got pesto.
Um, yeah, it has palm oil.
Is that bad?
Well, it's 50% saturated fat, so...
I thought fat was
a good thing now.
It... There's different kinds.
Can you take it back?
Sure. I just thought, for pasta, it'd...
Mom.
-So, what's your plan, then, as far as...
-Mom? Mom.
I'm speaking, Emma, okay?
-Can we go now?
-We just got here.
-I'm hungry. Mom.
-We're gonna get food, okay?
Um...
If you ever needed a babysitter,
even just for an afternoon
to really, you know,
nail the farmers' market...
-And you're in childcare?
-I am. Um...
I had mentioned it, you know,
but that was a long time ago.
I remember, yeah.
Let me see if I have your number.
Okay.
I mean,
she's had a rough go of it.
It's just easier to talk to her than,
like, half the moms at Emma's school.
She's just like an actual person.
But she has experience with kids?
Yeah. Yeah, I'll get a reference from her.
-Mom, not too short.
-I know. There you go.
-And you said you wanted a break.
-I do.
I could... I could go a bit easier
this time, and, um...
take care of myself,
like everybody's always demanding.
Okay.
Right.
What do you think?
Perfect.
Gold star.
Ooh. Why, thank you.
-Hello.
-Hi, Rosanna?
-Uh, yes.
-Hi. My name's Caitlin.
I... I got your number from Polly Murphy.
-Oh. Hi.
-Hi. Yeah.
We're considering hiring her as a nanny
and I was just curious
about your experience with her.
Oh, um...
She's amazing.
Really became a part of our family.
That's great to hear.
Sorry. How long
did she work for you?
-Gosh, a couple of years.
-Uh-huh.
Okay. Wow. That's great.
That's a... That's a really long time.
Yeah. Really wonderful with the kids.
Hi.
So, clean go here, and then
dirties straight in the dishwasher.
-There's a sterilized cycle.
-Okay.
And just glass bottles.
Right. Hold on the micro plastics.
Exactly. Yes, I know we're a lost cause,
but, you know, hopefully for them.
Uh, okay. Here.
-Oh, wow.
-Yeah, I've stocked up quite a lot.
So we've got left to right,
older to newer.
-So you can just pull from the left.
-And no formula?
For... Oh. No, that stuff is just sugar.
So once she has that... you know.
-Got it. Yeah.
-Okay.
Josie.
Josie, it's your new nanny, Polly.
-Want to say hi?
-Hi.
Hi.
Mommy says no sugar.
Hi, baby.
Hi baby.
So, I think, um,
I'm gonna go run some errands.
Great. Yeah.
Um...
-We'll be fine.
-Right.
Okay.
Bye.
♪ She talks to birds
She talks to angels ♪
♪ She talks to trees
She talks to bees ♪
♪ She don't talk to me ♪
♪ Talks to the rainbows
and to the seas... ♪
Jesus!
-Hello.
-Food's here.
-Great.
-Josie's asleep, so I'm gonna head home.
-Great. Okay.
Uh, do you want dinner?
-Yeah.
-I mean, there's plenty.
Please, stay.
-Stay.
-Okay.
I'll go get another plate.
Here you go.
Oh, I don't drink.
Cool. Um, my love.
Great. Thank you. Okay.
All right. This looks good.
-Emma, you want the chicken?
-Have whatever you want, just dig in.
Okay.
I need space!
Emma...
You can have space,
but you cannot speak to me in that...
My God! Leave me alone!
Should you just give her a second?
Yeah.
She thinks I'm this controlling,
like, scold.
It's 'cause all the other parents
are scared of their own kids.
I see that a lot.
Emma's smart, but she is super willful.
Ever since she was a baby,
if I set her down even for one second,
she would just scream.
-Scream.
-Sounds so hard.
Yeah, that first year was,
um, was something.
Hey, you know what?
Don't let me keep you. Really.
-If you need to...
-Oh. No, it's just, um...
this girl.
We've been sort of talking.
Oh, yeah? You like her?
I'm not sure yet.
It's, um...
It's funny. I was dating a woman
when I met Miguel.
I think I could tell that.
Really?
About me?
Yeah. You have that vibe to you.
-I think this is going back.
-I like it.
Do you want it?
I mean, maybe it looks better on you.
Okay.
Let's see.
Oh, yeah.
I'm sorry. Is that weird? I...
No. No, I... I love it.
You know what?
Um, I'll grab you some scissors.
Cut the tag.
Miguel, um,
can we try tonight?
Maybe? I'm just not... I'm not...
-Right now.
-Okay.
I'm sorry. I've missed you, too, you know?
I've missed you, too.
It's just Josie, and...
It's fine.
It's okay.
Oh, you know what, I have that, um...
stop sign meeting this afternoon.
Mm-hmm.
Could you take Emma to basketball?
I can't. I'm meeting with the builders.
Okay.
Why don't you ask Polly to take her?
It's walking distance.
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
I have a surprise for you.
-Don't tell.
-I won't.
Do you want some, Josie? I bet you do.
Here. Mm.
Give her some.
It's so much sugar.
It's good for you.
Mm.
Did your mom let you eat sugar?
She did.
She made the best cupcakes.
But before I got too old,
she had to go away.
But your dad could stay?
Nope.
The place I went to live,
the only thing they had to eat
was tuna fish.
-That's silly.
-It is.
But it gets even sillier than that.
There was no mayonnaise, no lettuce,
no bread even.
I had to eat the tuna
out of a can, like a cat.
And when there was no more left...
there was nothing left to eat.
Whoa! Whoo!
Whee!
Whoa!
Oh, my goodness.
Whoa. Wow.
She's so beautiful.
She is.
Ready?
Emergency.
There's smoke in the kitchen.
-Smoke alarm detected in the kitchen.
-Okay.
What are you making?
Uh, cioppino.
It's like a fish stew.
Huh.
Hey, I can cook.
Okay? I'm cooking. I can cook.
It's just Stewart coming, right?
Uh, I think he's bringing Bethany.
I mean, we could just get In-N-Out
and tacos or something.
You can't invite people over to dinner
and then just get In-N-Out.
-Come on.
-Oh, I think this is burning.
-Okay. Shit.
-Oh, boy.
Out of my kitchen. Out.
Everybody out of my kitchen.
Okay, chapino.
Cioppino. We're getting banished.
But that's assuming
that a police presence reduces crime.
Or that it helps at all
at resolving disputes.
I mean, there are studies
that show the opposite.
-What studies?
-What?
What studies?
There are multiple.
I can't cite one.
Okay, so say somebody
broke into your house,
you would, what?
Honestly, I mean, I would grab my bat
before I would call the police
or do anything.
-Stewart.
-I'm serious.
Obviously, the first priority
would be my partner and I's safety.
But take the cash, take the TV.
The stuff isn't...
But, Stewart, what if they wanted
your Ted Williams rookie card?
What would you do?
Well, then I would know
that the person under the ski mask is you.
You bitch.
Apologies, to everyone at the table.
Polly, I hear you guys met
at one of our tenants' rights events.
-Yeah.
-Mm.
Um...
Where is your place?
Oh, I live in Boyle Heights.
Oh, nice. Uh, why way out there?
Well, that's what I can afford.
Oh, I get you.
-Where do you live?
-Oh, Silver Lake.
Mm.
I get ya.
Anyways, I'm actually
thinking about moving.
Just, LA's so expensive.
You mean, like, outside of Los Angeles?
Yeah.
I just... I don't know
how long I can stay here for.
Can I be done?
Well, you're not watching TV,
if that's what you're after.
-I can go hang with her.
-Yeah.
Yeah. Okay, great. Thank you.
The soup is so good, by the way.
-Mm-hmm.
-Oh, good.
Oh, my God.
Look at this little angel eating soup.
Yeah. It's really interesting.
The sooner you start them
on real food, the better.
You know, because baby food
can be such a crutch.
Ugh, tell me about it. I've been trying
to wean myself off baby food for a while.
I want one.
-Can we talk about this later?
-Mm-hmm.
Thank you.
Mommy!
Oh, God.
-Oh, she threw up.
-Oh, no. I know, baby.
I'm sorry, baby.
Oh, God, I'm gonna...
I don't know what happened.
I figure it was the food.
Yeah, no shit.
Should we call Stewart?
Oh, no.
Oh, God, Josie. Oh, God.
How's Emma?
She's doing better. She's with Miguel now.
How is she?
They need to get her hydrated.
It just doesn't matter how hard I try.
How careful I am.
I just always fuck everything up.
I fuck everything up.
You're wrong.
Yeah, you don't know me.
Yes, I do.
You think if you try hard enough,
you can stop bad things from happening.
But you can't.
Nobody can.
God, you're so cold. Here.
-Oh, thank you.
-Here, okay.
I don't want you to go.
I don't want to either.
I just...
I don't think I have a choice.
Bye, Polly.
♪ The sun, the sun
The sun was rising from the field ♪
♪ I got a feeling I just can't shake ♪
♪ I got a feeling
that just won't go away ♪
♪ You've got to just keep on pushing it ♪
♪ Keep on pushing it ♪
♪ Push the sky away ♪
So what? You don't think we should?
It's not that.
If you think it'll help having her here...
Yeah, I do.
What? What is it?
I'm just thinking about
after Emma was born.
Okay. I was spiraling out.
-It happens to a lot of women after birth.
-I know. I know.
It's just...
What?
You have this confidence about you,
and I really didn't know
what a hard time you were having until...
I think you're making a bigger deal
out of it than it was.
You ripped the kitchen apart, Caitlin.
-I ripped it apart?
-Yeah.
-Okay.
-At 4:00 in the morning,
you had everything on the floor
and a bottle of bleach.
Fine. Fine.
Do you remember what you said to me?
I think I said something like,
there was a smell, which there was,
and that it could have been mold.
You said our lives were in danger.
And, I don't know, I guess
if you're feeling that way again...
I'm not.
Miguel...
I'm not, okay? I'm okay.
Okay.
Are you okay?
Because I'm okay.
I'm just saying.
It's a really
sweet little space.
I think you'll like it.
-It's, um, got its own kitchen.
-Okay.
And its own entrance up here,
so you can come and go as you like.
And you just have to make it your own.
Okay, this is it.
Miguel really wanted his parents
to move here, you know, to be safer.
But, um, his mom's not
the biggest fan of the States.
Who is?
What do you think?
It's perfect.
Great.
Um, yes, you've got
a closet here, shelves.
This a good spot for your coffee?
Yeah, that's fine. It's perfect. Yeah.
Emma.
Say bye-bye.
Bye-bye.
Yeah.
Hey.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Um, it's 8:30, so I just was wondering
if I should put Emma to bed.
-Wow, it's 8:30?
-Yeah.
Is something tight?
-Um...
I know this technique
that might help.
-Okay.
-Okay. Just turn around.
Let's see.
Okay. It's gonna hurt a little bit.
There you go.
Thank you.
Yeah.
I should... I should put Emma to bed.
Okay. Yeah.
I'm sorry.
I just... I couldn't resist.
Hey, go back to sleep.
I can listen up for Josie.
It's fine.
It's okay.
What?
Nothing.
Okay.
What do you think?
I love it.
Just like the one you made for Emma.
She wouldn't let her friends sit in it.
Is that formula?
Yeah.
I know. I know
most people don't care about that.
Hi.
Um...
I found this in the trash.
You haven't...
I mean, you didn't
feed this to Josie, right?
Oh. Yeah. I've been having a hard time
getting her to drink the breast milk.
So...
I'm just confused because we had talked
about not feeding her sugar at all.
We did?
Yes.
Oh, I'm so sorry, Caitlin.
I-I didn't remember that.
-You...
-It's...
Whatever you want.
It's just, she might drink
a little bit less.
-It's just, I clearly remember that we...
-Mom...
We were playing.
Right. Sorry.
Recently.
Where should we begin?
We've been focusing on the secrets,
the stuff we push under the rug,
conversations that we are known to have,
and certainly not in the public square.
The forbidden.
Well, multiple times a week.
Right. Otherwise...
Otherwise, well, a lot of things.
Depression, anxiety,
prostate cancer.
-Cancer?
-Mm-hmm.
And your source on this
is some high school boyfriend?
-Hey.
This is my friend, Amelia.
Nice to meet you.
Caitlin. Mm.
They, um... They got burgers.
I'm stealing some.
Yeah. Yeah, I see that.
You're really treating yourselves.
Uh, I mean,
we have more if you want some.
No, no, no. I'm good.
-You sure?
-Yeah.
Uh, I'm just gonna take a shower, I think.
Night.
What about women?
-Ah, it's different.
-No, they're not.
I have to ask more questions for that one.
-Can you follow instructions?
-Mm-hmm.
Don't move.
You're gonna make me fucking cum.
Choke me.
Who's Olivia?
She's my little sister.
Mm.
-Good morning.
-Hi.
Your coffee's ready.
Guess who got four ounces in?
What?
Of breast milk.
We're back on track.
Great.
Okay. I think it's looking better.
Perfect. Gold star.
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
-Whoo!
What does "depressed" mean?
It means that you're sad,
that you don't like yourself.
Is that like my mom?
No.
She's angry.
-At me?
-No.
-At me.
-Why?
I know a secret about her.
And when you know a secret about someone,
you hold power over them.
People don't like that.
What's the secret?
She's pretending to be someone else.
Who is she?
Not who she's pretending to be.
Hi, Leah.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
This is Caitlin.
Of course. Caitlin.
Sorry about that.
Uh, I've been having a weird reaction
to my medication lately.
It's been making me feel
a little bit jittery.
Well, we could lower the dose.
You want to try taking half a pill
for a week and see how that goes?
So you just want to lower the dose
based on that one comment?
Well, it's whatever
you're comfortable with, Caitlin.
Shit.
And right in the middle
of his science lecture...
...Mr. Hutcherson sneezed
and he spat all over Nicole's face.
And she tried,
like, wiping it off with her T-shirt.
That's so gross. Mmh-mmh.
Yeah, it was hilarious.
Mom?
Mm-hmm?
I've been having these feelings.
You know, in a movie,
when people are getting married
or when they're kissing
or trying to make a baby?
When I watch that, I want to be
the daddy, the husband.
Okay, um...
So, are you saying
you wish you were a man?
No. I wish...
I want to be kissing the woman.
I want her to love me, not him.
Listen, um, you're getting into that age
where you're gonna start having
all kinds of feelings, um,
-and I think whatever decision you make...
-No, it's not a decision.
Okay? We're not saying that.
No, but I have. I've decided.
When I grow up, I want to have a wife,
not a husband.
Is this something
that you two have talked about?
Um...
Well, she just had asked me
about, you know, marriage
and the types of couples that there are.
She's never said
anything like this to me before.
So I think that maybe...
Mom, I think this.
I'm saying this.
Of course. And we hear you.
But maybe you overheard Polly
saying this and you're...
Caitlin, it wasn't that, okay?
Can you stop talking for a second?
You want me to stay a baby forever,
but I'm not! I'm not a baby!
I hate you!
I'm...
I'm so sorry, Caitlin.
-I did not think you'd have a problem...
-I don't have a problem with it!
Obviously.
Well, um, I'm gonna go check on her.
It's okay. She'll get over it.
You don't think it's strange?
-She's getting older. She's...
-She's ten.
-How old were you when you started...
-Why are you asking me that?
-I'm just trying to understand.
-It has nothing to do with me.
She's... She's too young. That's it.
And you're not here.
You don't see what's been happening.
They go into her room.
They're in there for hours,
and we don't know what they're doing
or what they're talking about.
You're saying...
all the attention
that Emma has been giving her,
how close they've gotten,
it's making you jealous.
Well, that sounds bad.
-Like...
-No, no, no. It's not bad at all.
It's not bad.
It's just been us the whole time.
Now there's this new person in the house.
It's weird.
Honey, I get it.
I guess there's just
this part of me that's like...
What?
I don't want her to grow up, you know?
I just want her to stay mine.
I want her to be mine.
Um...
That's just...
sick.
Oh, honey.
That one looks so cool.
-It's huge.
-The red and orange ones?
-Wow.
-Yeah. Those are beautiful.
You wanna go check out over there?
Oh, okay.
We're gonna go for a walk.
Okay.
You okay?
Yeah.
It's nice.
Do you want some help cleaning up?
Sure.
You're, um...
You're wearing the dress I gave you.
Yeah.
Looks nice.
Oh, thanks.
Mom! Mom!
-Mom! Fireworks!
-Get down! Get down!
What happened? What happened?
Where did you get that from? Answer me!
-I don't know.
-Caitlin, don't.
Do you have any idea
what could have happened?
Stop it! Look at her. She's terrified.
-Polly!
-It's okay. It's okay.
I'm sorry. I got them at the park.
Why would you do that?
I thought it'd be fun.
I didn't think she...
-Fun?
-It was an accident, okay?
-What's the matter with you?
-What?
She did it on purpose.
Why can't you see that?
-Why would she do that?
-She knew what would happen.
-She wanted this to happen.
-I just think...
You know, maybe I should go.
Yeah? Yeah. Leave!
Let's take a break and we can all...
No, no. Leave!
Leave this house!
Mom, it was my fault.
I mean, if that's what you want.
-Wait. Let's just please...
-No, no.
Do you need me to do this myself?
Because I will.
-Where is she gonna go?
-I don't care!
Not here!
What are you doing? Go! Pack!
-Okay. It's okay. All right? I'm sorry.
-No, Polly.
I'm sorry.
Polly...
Miguel.
What?
Do you believe me?
Por Dios, no puede ser.
Do you?
Believe you about what?
That she did it on purpose,
that she knew what would happen.
No, that's...
What? You think she just gave her
fucking fireworks and it's fine?
I think it was a mistake.
Okay?
-She just wanted to have fun.
-Ugh.
Yeah, of course you'd think that.
What?
Why?
Because I'm Mexican?
I can't help myself?
I fucking love fireworks?
No.
No. Because no matter what I say,
you won't listen to me
because you think I'm a fucking nutcase
that you need to handle.
No, no, no.
You're...
You're struggling again.
It's not your fault.
But I can't help you
if you're not willing to see
the possibility that you could be wrong.
Can you see that possibility?
I don't know.
I need you to try.
Or what?
Miguel.
Okay.
Do you...
Do you know where she went?
Happy fucking new year to you!
Why do you do this to me?
Hey, come on, man.
Hey, man. I'm fucking serious.
Hey, hey!
Shut up!
I'm sorry.
I, um...
I've had some issues in the past, and I...
I thought
that I had dealt with them, but...
I understand.
But I have a handle on that now, so...
Caitlin, you're not crazy.
You know what we need?
More data.
It's getting better. I, um...
I just need to keep focusing...
What do you know about her?
I mean, besides what she's told you?
I mean, you can...
You can think something,
but that doesn't...
That doesn't make it real.
Look, what are we gonna find out?
Probably that everything's normal.
So why not just take a look. All right?
You're my favorite psycho.
Hi.
They finally finished
the renovations in here.
They did a good job.
Glad you approve.
-Sorry. I'll get out of your hair.
-Listen.
I know this is their house, and,
well, you're their friend, but...
Well, this feels like...
my space, so...
And you don't want people
just coming in and out.
Have a good day.
You have reached the voice mailbox
for 515-177-3...
Oh.
-Here you are.
-Hi.
Uh, is there more breast milk?
I looked in the freezer, there's nothing.
Oh, uh...
What are you doing in here anyway?
Nothing. I just need to finish something.
Okay.
Should I give her formula?
Don't give her... No, can... Um...
Can you just take her for five minutes
and I'll be right in?
Sure.
-Oh, my God.
-Found a week later.
Rosanna?
-Yes.
-Hi, um, I'm Caitlin.
I called you a while back about Polly.
She nannied for you.
I know who you are.
Can I talk to you for a second?
Sure.
-Is Polly okay?
-Yeah, she's fine.
She's been involved in some dangerous
incidents with my children, so...
Listen, Polly hasn't returned
my calls for a while.
If she's using again,
her behavior probably is erratic.
So, she met you here then, is that right?
And she told you what?
She told you she's an addict?
Yes.
And I made a promise to help her
however I could.
Did she ever even work for you?
-Did she take care of your kids?
-Sh...
Yes, she did.
You're lying.
You know, if you had any idea
what Polly's been through...
Really? Like what?
Like when I met her,
she was living in her car,
and had a boyfriend who beat her up
so bad she had to go to the hospital.
Okay. And you just believed her,
is that right?
What? Listen, I have a meeting here.
I'm so sorry about your meeting.
You lied to me.
You put my children in danger!
-Do you even care about that?
-I do.
-And I'm trying...
-What if nothing she told you is true?
What then?
Are you gonna answer me?
-Okay. I'm gonna ask you to leave.
-I'm going!
Hey, uh, it's Stewart.
Um, give me a call when you get this.
I, uh... I think we should talk.
Hey.
I need to talk to you.
Where'd you go?
Out. I needed to check on something.
Okay. What?
She's lying to us.
That reference she gave,
she never even worked for her.
How do you know?
Because I chased the woman down
and I spoke to her.
And what?
She said, "Polly didn't work for me"?
No. No, of course not.
I-I cornered her at this AA meeting,
which is where they met, by the way,
and then she lied to me again...
That's what you were doing?
Your baby's hungry.
-Oh, my God, I'm sorry...
-And she's sleeping.
I'm fucking done. Let's talk tomorrow.
Hi.
You want to come in?
Um...
Could you tell me
what this is about first?
I owe you an apology.
I had you wrong.
And if you're okay with it,
I would like the opportunity to explain.
You can have a seat anywhere.
-Can I get you something to drink?
-I'm good.
Uh...
What's that?
Well, it's information.
About me?
Yeah.
Like what?
Well, I know your real name,
Rebecca.
So, you went through my things.
Yes, I did.
And I know that you grew up
in San Bernardino, like Caitlin.
But her name wasn't Caitlin.
It was Jennifer.
Jenny.
And I know when you were seven,
you lost everything,
your whole family, in a fire.
Yes.
I can't begin to imagine...
what that must have been like.
No.
In context here, it's important.
I mean,
there's no true version of the story
that leaves out what you've been through.
Yes, there is.
That's what happened.
She killed my parents,
my baby sister,
and nothing happened to her.
They changed her name and sent her away.
I mean, something happened to her
before the fire.
No, that's not true.
Regardless, I hope we can agree
that what you're doing to her now,
to her husband, to her daughters,
that is not right either, is it?
Did you tell her?
No. I wanted to talk to you first.
But if you don't, I will.
Uh...
I feel sick.
Um, can I use the bathroom?
Yeah, of course. Um...
It's straight through the doorway here,
just straight ahead.
Buddy.
You got this.
Rebecca... Polly,
can I get you anything?
If it were me,
I would want the same thing you want,
to see her suffer. But...
I would hope that
there would be someone there
to just sympathize,
and end the cycle of...
Had to get in there.
Had to be the savior.
You made me do this.
I hope you realize that.
-Hello?
-Caitlin, it's Bethany.
-I'm at the hospital.
-What is it? What...
It's Stewart.
There was a break-in. He's...
-Oh, my God.
-He's really hurt.
Okay, I'm coming.
I'm coming now. I'm coming.
What's going on?
-It's Stewart.
-What happened?
-He's been attacked. Just...
-Oh, my God.
-Stay with the kids, okay?
-Okay.
-Hi.
-What's going on?
I'm sorry. Who are you?
I'm his best friend. How is he?
-He...
-He's in a tough situation,
given how he came in.
So I went to his house
and I opened the door,
and then he was just...
He was just lying there on the ground,
and there was so much blood.
-And then his jaw was just...
-The head trauma?
-Yes.
-The break-in?
-Uh...
Sorry, officer.
I need to speak with you.
Let me get your number,
and then I can put you in contact
with the detective in charge.
Stewart thought that a woman
named Polly Murphy,
that she was lying to me
and lying to my family.
-And he was looking into her.
-Wait. Polly?
-You mean your nanny?
-Yes.
He believed me, Stewart.
He believed me, and she knew that.
I'll get you in contact with the officer.
I need you...
I'm trying to tell you
what's going on here!
Please, listen to me.
Ma'am, please lower your voice. Thank you.
Come with me. Let's go.
I'm really sorry.
I'm... I'm gonna go to the chapel, okay?
I'll be back.
How is he?
Ask her.
-Okay. What do you...
-Get out!
-Stop it.
-You can go, too, if you want.
Mom.
She's just upset about her friend.
Stop talking to her and get out!
Now!
Oh, fine. Fine.
Caitlin.
-Caitlin, listen to me.
-No.
I'm done. I'm done!
Caitlin, stop! Will you...
What are you doing?
-You, stop it!
-Will you...
-Will you stop?
-Let me do it!
You get away from her!
-Caitlin, stop!
-Mom, what are you doing?
-Stop! Get off!
-Get off me!
No! No.
You okay?
Let me see. Let me see.
You're hurt, Emma.
I wanna see. Let me.
Let me see. Let me see. You okay?
Come on. We'll get you up. Come on.
Let's get you in the house.
What we need to do is
separate the incident with Polly and Emma,
which could lead to a restraining order.
What about Stewart?
Caitlin, I'm very sorry
you lost your friend,
-but it's not going to help us.
-He texted me.
And then he called her,
the last person, before he died.
-She has to...
-That's being investigated.
-We just need you to be patient.
-Fine.
Fine. I just want to see my kids now.
Today. I want to see them today.
The good news is,
Miguel is willing to make that happen.
But you need to understand,
he does still need her
to help with the kids.
You did the right thing
moving out last week,
but honestly, Caitlin,
in light of what happened,
the judge could raise the issue
of the children's safety
-when they're in your care.
-They're unsafe now!
They are with her now!
No!
It's okay, sweetheart.
Mom's here.
All right. Come on, baby. Let's go.
Come on, go.
Come on.
-Hey.
Did you stretch?
Not yet.
-Here's this.
-Thanks.
Where's Josie?
She was napping.
-We agreed I could see her.
-You will.
Dad, you staying for my game?
That's fine with me.
Okay.
I'll, um... I'll go get us seats.
You're mad at me.
That's good. That's good. You should be.
I'm hard on you, Emma.
And I know I watch you too closely.
I think because
nobody really watched out for me.
But that's not your fault, okay?
It's not your fault.
Nobody watched out for you?
No.
I found this in Polly's room.
I actually stole it.
Mom... Look...
It says a different name, but...
that's Polly.
See?
She's from where you're from.
She's an orphan.
That's why she tries so hard
to be in our family.
So you can come back now?
Is that what you want?
Players to the court.
I'm trying, honey.
Come on. Come on, let's go.
Hi.
-Josie's still sleeping.
-Rebecca.
Do you want to come in?
You look like you could use some water.
Okay.
Way to box it out.
Hi, this is Caitlin.
I can't come to the phone right now.
Please leave a message.
Come on, guys. Whoo!
Emma. Emma, we need to go home.
-Why?
-Come on. We gotta go.
Nice, Kayla, nice.
I've dreamt about this.
Meeting you.
But I guess you've dreamt
about it even more.
Yes.
What should I say?
I'm sorry for what happened.
For what I did.
I, uh... I told the school
and I told my dad...
...what your father was doing to me,
and nobody believed me.
-Because you were lying.
-No.
No, he hurt me.
And he wouldn't stop.
That's bullshit.
You pretend like you're this good person.
But you're not.
I've tried to be but...
But you're trying to hide it
from everyone, from your family.
But you can't.
You don't know anything about me.
You never even met me back then.
Oh, but I saw you...
that night.
My parents.
My sister was a baby.
And you cried and whined
about what happened to you.
They believed you then, didn't they?
-They did.
-You know what I got?
I got seven different houses.
-It wasn't right...
-Because of you!
Because of what you did to me.
Look at me.
Do you know
how much pain you caused me?
But you know I wasn't lying.
You know.
Because he did it to you, too.
He told me.
No.
How much we looked alike.
-That we could be sisters.
-No.
I've thought about you every single day.
What you've suffered,
what I took from you.
You were alone with nothing.
Stop.
Just please believe me.
I know how that feels.
I'm here now.
I'm here for whatever you want to say.
What...
What I want...
...is for you to rot in hell...
...while I sleep in your bed...
...and fuck your husband,
and raise your beautiful daughters.
Okay, baby.
Hi. This is Caitlin.
-I can't come to the phone...
-Dad.
Come on, Emma.
What's happening?
It's okay, baby.
It's okay. It's okay.
Get out! Get out of the car!
It's okay.
Stop! No!
Oh, my God! Caitlin!
Oh, my God.
Oh, God.
Oh, God. Caitlin.
-I'm okay.
-You're hurt.
I'm okay.
She's okay.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
Let me help you. Let me help you.
Give me the baby.
Come here, sweetheart. I got you.
I saw her.
I'm so sorry.
Forgive me.
I should have listened to you.
It's okay.
Please. Send help.
We need an ambulance.
Is she coming?
She's with Josie.
This kid, she knows everything.
It's gonna be okay.
We're gonna be okay.
So, it was her, her parents,
and her baby sister, Olivia.
But then one day she had to go
live all on her own.
And the place Rebecca went to,
there was nothing to eat but tuna fish.
It gets even sillier than that.
There was no mayonnaise,
no lettuce, no bread even.
She had to eat the tuna
out of a can like a cat.
Meow.
When there was no more left...
there was nothing left to eat.
♪ I'll be your mirror ♪
♪ Reflect what you are
In case you don't know ♪
♪ I'll be the wind
the rain, and the sunset ♪
♪ The light on your door
to show that you're home ♪
♪ When you think the night
has seen your mind ♪
♪ That inside, you're twisted and unkind ♪
♪ Let me stand to show
that you are blind ♪
♪ Please put down your hands ♪
♪ 'Cause I see you ♪
♪ I find it hard to believe
you don't know ♪
♪ The beauty you are ♪
♪ But if you don't, let me be your eyes ♪
♪ A hand to your darkness
so you won't be afraid ♪
♪ When you think the night
has seen your mind ♪
♪ That inside, you're twisted and unkind ♪
♪ Let me stand to show
that you are blind ♪
♪ Please put down your hands ♪
♪ 'Cause I see you ♪
-♪ I'll be your mirror ♪
-♪ Reflect what you are ♪